ALL NAMES, CHARACTERS,
AND EVENTS ARE FICTIONAL
CHILD AND ANIMAL WELFARE
REGULATIONS WERE OBSERVED
Sis.
You came to see the paintings.
You're doing just fine.
People would talk if they saw us together.
It's quiet here at least.
And…
we aren't related by blood,
so don't call me sister.
Come on.
I'm just grateful.
It's thanks to you that I was released.
Then we should settle the bill.
I heard Hwa-jin was here.
I'm not sure.
Why did you call Choi Myeong-ju then?
"Lee Hwa-jin is here."
Didn't you need someone to tattle to me?
I knew it.
You and I think alike.
Why are you keeping her?
Because I heard you were
desperately looking for her.
From whom?
My brother-in-law
got Lee Hwa-jin discharged,
and my sister was looking for her?
Why?
There must be a reason.
Where did the patient in Room 501 go?
I found that odd,
and the doctor who saw
her blood test result reacted strangely.
Is this accurate?
So I checked the blood test result again.
I found it strange too.
Why? What was strange?
Check the blood test result.
Here.
Lee Hwa-jin
is likely pregnant.
Pregnant?
About Hwa-jin.
At first glance, I thought,
"What the heck?"
But after getting her cleaned
and dolled up,
she was a sight to behold.
My brother-in-law
has an eye for women.
Is the baby…
It's his child?
You know I hate spoilers.
Answer me.
Well…
Go and ask her yourself.
She's waiting for you.
You know what, Sis?
Two hundred and sixty-six days.
They say it takes a whole 266 days
from getting pregnant to giving birth.
That's 6,384 hours.
I'm good at math, you know.
That's a long time.
What are you doing? Come on.
I never understood
why you and Min-cheol kept going on
about how one person had to change
or be saved.
Then I learned
that it takes 266 days.
It takes 6,384 hours.
Now I get
why you said one person is one world.
It makes sense.
I get it now.
Two ahead. You go first.
-I'm going in.
-Go.
Seon U-yeong!
-Stop there, you punk!
-Hey!
What's going on?
Darn it.
Stop there!
Move!
Stay still.
Hey, get off of me.
Seon U-yeong,
you're under arrest for theft.
You have the right to an attorney,
and to remain silent.
I didn't do anything.
I don't know anything.
Get up.
Oh, for goodness' sake.
-U-yeong.
-It's not what you think.
Something went wrong.
-U-yeong.
-I'm not guilty. Don't worry.
Why are you doing this?
What did U-yeong do?
We can talk in Haseong Police Station.
Sir!
This can be considered
obstruction of justice.
Su-mi, wait at home.
I'll clear up the misunderstanding
and go home.
-Let's go, Detective.
-Move.
U-yeong.
Let go!
You need the chairman's approval.
I said I'd be right back.
No, you can't!
Is it this dress?
Because of this darn dress?
I'll take it off and go then.
Geez.
Hi, Su-mi.
U-yeong is
in Haseong Police Station, right?
I'll be right there.
Stop her.
-Move.
-No, ma'am.
I said, move.
Hey, stop her.
I said I'd be right back!
Let go of me!
Let go!
What…
What's going on?
Hey. Hey!
What the…
God damn it.
Hey.
What happened to her?
We didn't do anything.
She wanted to go out,
so we tried to stop her,
and she suddenly passed out.
Sis, what do we do?
Sis.
Is she dead?
Is she alive?
What are you doing?
Just stay.
Ma'am.
The doctor said you needed to rest.
So lie down.
I need to go. Someone's waiting for me.
It's for the baby too.
I heard you're pregnant.
How do you
know that?
I said, lie down.
Ma'am, I need your help.
Please get U-yeong out
of the police station.
He didn't do anything wrong.
Please tell them that the necklace was
just a present for me.
Necklace?
I'm doomed.
I'm doomed now. What do I do?
Is Su-mi really doomed?
I saw this coming
when she was going overboard.
U-yeong, what do I do?
Could you sell this for me?
Where did you get this?
-Did you…
-Don't ask anything.
Just take care of it quietly.
Okay.
But how much should I charge for this?
Just enough to get back what Su-mi lost.
Right. There's this guy
I got to know in juvie.
He's an expert in this area. I'll ask him.
I'm sorry.
For what?
It was my fault
that you went to juvie.
It was thanks to you.
I got to be in a place like that
thanks to you.
If I hadn't met you,
my life would've been so boring.
So Ji-yu was right.
Ji-yu told me that
you must've stolen the necklace.
She said she saw you search our closet
with the lights off on the election day.
That's not true.
I did steal the necklace,
but not on that day.
Then when did you steal it?
And why did you steal it?
Why that necklace of all things?
Because I saw you and Ji-yu
talk about the necklace.
I figured it'd be expensive.
I didn't plan to steal it, though.
I just…
I just wanted to try it on once.
Just like Ji-yu did.
FEBRUARY 8, 2027
-When you turn 20?
-Yes.
No, that's insane.
You turning 20?
Come on. Three years will fly by.
So please keep it safe until then.
Okay.
Then I'll keep it well until then.
Oh, wait.
Let me see it once again.
Here.
It looks great on you.
Congratulations on starting high school.
Thank you.
Yes, I just got home.
I forgot about the dress code.
I'll just grab my tie real quick.
Then Mr. Hyun suddenly came in.
I panicked and then passed out.
Just like today.
Like today?
Yes, just like today.
Hwa-jin.
Are you okay?
But I couldn't answer.
Because I passed out again.
Hwa-jin.
It doesn't happen a lot,
but it happens sometimes.
You know when you're half-asleep
and you just can't wake up
no matter how hard you try?
That's what it felt like.
Hwa-jin.
I saw what you two did.
-It's not what you think.
-What are you talking about?
It's nothing like what you think.
There was an accident like today,
and I was worried about her--
I said I saw everything!
I saw it.
Then Ji-yu must've seen that
and misunderstood.
Misunderstood? Misunderstood what?
Never mind.
So he came in
when you were trying the necklace on,
and then you passed out?
Yes.
And then?
What happened next?
Hwa-jin, are you okay?
Sir.
Can you stand up?
Yes.
I didn't steal it.
I thought he wouldn't believe me
if I explained why I was wearing it.
So I thought I would just take it
and put it back later.
-Let me take you to the hospital.
-No, I'm okay.
I'm really okay.
This happens every now and then.
The doctor said it's okay too.
It's called
vasovagal something.
It sounds like a serious illness,
but it's just fainting.
Are you sure you're okay?
I'm totally fine now.
That's why I went back
to the walk-in closet
saying that I'd left my phone there.
It was to put the necklace back.
It's true.
Do you expect me to believe that?
It's true. Please believe me.
You told Ji-yu
it was to find the pendant you'd lost.
That was
just an excuse.
You asked her to give the pendant back,
and Ji-yu refused to.
Then you tried to take it from her,
which led to the accident.
Then what did you and he talk about
at the parking lot
when you got the pendant back?
Parking lot?
He gave you the pendant back
at the parking lot.
I got the pendant back
from Secretary Shin, not Mr. Hyun.
What? Secretary Shin?
Here.
I forgot to give it back.
He wants to give this back to you.
Right.
You want me to drive you home?
Yes, I just want to get changed first.
What's the address?
It's close from here.
Building A, Urban Tree,
82 Gyojeong-ro, Haseong.
So it was Secretary Shin
that he handed the pendant to.
I misunderstood.
I thought it was you.
Pardon?
So you asked your friend
to sell the necklace?
I'm sorry.
I urgently needed money.
And you're asking me
to help to release the friend
who got arrested for selling it.
Yes, just saying that it was a gift
would do.
Why should I?
Why should I lie just to help you?
I'll do anything I can
to return your favor.
How?
With money?
Do you have money?
Not at the moment,
but I'll pay you back somehow.
I'll do whatever you say.
Whatever?
I'll do whatever you want me to do.
So please…
Please get U-yeong out.
You're pregnant, right?
Yes.
But what about it?
Who's the father?
Who's the father of the baby?
I'm heading out first.
It's going to rain today.
Don't forget your umbrella.
It's the real Indian curry, your favorite.
Don't order delivery food like last time.
Microwave it for two minutes,
take it out, stir it,
and then microwave it for one more minute.
Then it'll heat evenly and taste better.
Don't forget to eat these too.
Or you're upsetting these guys.
CHICKEN DELIVERY
-You haven't eaten yet, right?
-No, I was going to.
I was about to microwave the curry.
No, don't eat that.
Why not?
Could you wait a little?
Let's eat together.
Go wash up.
Come on. Eat up.
Is it someone's birthday today?
Birthday?
Why?
Don't you think this is a little too much?
It's not too much.
If only I weren't so busy,
I could easily make a dozen side dishes.
Even just now,
I put together a whole meal in no time.
What do you think? Do you like it?
Yes, it's tasty.
But this is definitely too much.
I mean, look at me.
I feel so lost at the table.
Gang-myeong, you're so sweet.
But
make sure it's just for me.
Don't be like that to other girls. Okay?
-What are you saying?
-"What are you saying?"
Don't do that.
Fine. It's because it was so cute.
Here. Have some mackerel. You like it.
I was already eating it.
Don't you see I'm getting chubby here?
Your dad used to say that a lot.
You remember it.
Of course.
Everything he said
and every prank he played on me…
I remember them all,
even though I was only seven.
Remember me too, okay?
What are you talking about?
I'm just jealous.
I'll be jealous if you don't remember me
like you remember your dad.
This won't do. You should have some beer.
-Can I?
-Alcohol is the best cure for jealousy.
My boy is so smart.
Give me one second.
Thanks.
AIDE LIM HYUN-GYO
Hello? What is it at this hour?
Work?
Yes, it's work.
I'm having dinner with my son.
Why don't we meet another time?
Later, let's talk about it later.
This is nice.
Probably because my son poured it.
Are you sure you don't need to go?
The beer my son poured for me
tastes so good.
It must be even better
if I drink with him.
I can't wait.
Didn't you say not to grow up fast?
With all the nice things you've done,
you've done your part as a son.
So once you turn 20,
drink beer, make a girlfriend…
Do anything you want.
You're so fickle.
Oh, I forgot.
I made japchae
and forgot to put it on the table.
Give me one second. Keep eating.
Mom, you got a text.
I'm on my way to your place now.
It won't take long.
Darn it.
I've become
so out of shape.
I said later,
but you even came to my place.
What's so urgent?
I heard you quit.
I thought we could grab a drink
since we're both left out.
What do you mean?
Cha Su-yeon totally
stabbed me in the back.
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
She asked me
to block the special act
and reverse our party's stance.
So I took it upon myself.
Come on, don't look at me like that.
All my life,
I've lived in the shadow of others.
So I wanted to step
into the light for once.
That's why.
In exchange
for reversing the party's stance,
what did she demand?
If she did, I wouldn't be this upset.
Well…
At least I proved my influence
by reversing the party's stance.
So I was thinking of using that
to get a few assemblymen elected
in the general election.
Then she backstabbed me,
using that as an excuse.
Can you believe that?
The next general election
and presidential election?
You had too big a dream.
Reflecting on it only upsets me more.
I am
going to
return the favor.
What's your plan?
You came to talk to me,
so you must have a plan.
Cha Su-yeon
has got dirt
on a lot of my party's assemblymen.
She sort of inherited that
from his father.
I just need to get hold of the ledger.
What makes you think I'll help you?
Come on. You got fired too.
When you were
just about to join the Cabinet.
There must be something you want
out of frustration.
Why don't you join my party?
We can team up and start over.
If we manage to convince
the assemblymen with the ledger,
can we get
the special act passed?
The Do Tae-hun Special Act?
Can you reverse the party's stance again?
Wait.
You wanted the special act too?
Why?
Wasn't that what President-elect wanted?
That's why I proposed to him
that I'd shift my party's stance for him.
But he kept dragging his feet. Goodness.
You proposed to him,
but he didn't accept it?
That's why I've ended up like this.
In a situation where every second matters,
he took his time to think.
That's how Cha Su-yeon got me good.
Darn it.
You're saying President-elect
really didn't accept your offer.
I'm telling you.
He's terrible at seizing the right moment.
He's helpless at that.
So you just need the ledger?
I can change my party's stance using that.
But there's one more thing
we need to consider.
What is it?
A few days ago, Cha Su-yeon started
getting people in your party on her side.
Think about it. I shift my party's stance,
and your party's assemblymen
end up backing out.
That could actually happen.
I'll handle it myself.
I'll keep the party members' votes
under control
and get the ledger.
Really?
Secretary Shin,
you're ready to go all out.
I like it. You're fierce.
My goodness.
SHAMAN SEON
Excuse me.
Hello?
Did you get in touch with Hwa-jin?
Secretary Shin, please help me.
Please help my brother.
HASEONG POLICE STATION
Okay, to summarize what you said,
you don't remember
where or how you got the necklace.
Are you listening to me?
You don't even remember that
but sold it to Jang Hong-seok for 3 mill?
I didn't get the money yet.
He was supposed to sell--
"I'll pay you
after selling the stolen goods." Right?
Stop, stop!
Hello.
Forget about anything and everything
that's been said.
From now on, I decide
what you can and cannot say.
Open that mouth only when I allow you to.
Are you a lawyer?
Yes, I am.
I am Seon U-yeong's legal representative,
Lawyer Kang Seon-ho.
"Seon" here doesn't mean "kind."
It means "vicious."
LAWYER
KANG SEON-HO
You're the lawyer that was on TV.
Ms. Cha's divorce lawyer?
Yes, that's me.
It is me, but right now,
I'm Seon U-yeong's lawyer.
I'm sorry. A famous lawyer isn't
exactly helpful to a client.
But I got a bit famous, you see.
But he even refused a public defender.
I don't need a lawyer.
I submitted a letter of engagement
Ms. Seon Su-mi signed.
I don't need you.
Listen, Mr. Seon.
I said, I don't want a lawyer!
I'm allergic to lawyers.
Detective.
Can you give us ten minutes?
I don't need you here. Get lost.
I'm here because Hwa-jin asked.
Just ten minutes, please.
I'll briefly explain the right
to legal defense to my client.
The whole day of interrogation
was for nothing.
Sure, let's do that, Mr. Lawyer.
I'll be back in ten.
Explain his rights to him.
Hello?
It's Kang Seon-ho.
We met in the hospital just now.
As you said, Hwa-jin, he hated me
when I said I was a lawyer.
A hospital?
Is Hwa-jin sick? Did she faint again?
I'll put him on the phone. Talk to him.
Hey, Hwa-jin. Are you sick?
Why are you in a hospital?
Did you faint again?
U-yeong.
Yes. Are you hurt?
Are you okay?
Don't worry about me,
and do as the lawyer says.
I don't need a lawyer.
Just do exactly as the lawyer says.
Then you'll be released.
Hwa-jin.
Do as I say.
Put the lawyer on.
It's me.
He'll do as you say now.
Please make sure
U-yeong is released.
Okay, I'll try my best.
Mr. Seon, as I said earlier,
from now on, open that mouth of yours
only when I tell you to.
Do you understand?
It's done now.
Fortunately, the wound healed nicely.
Despite keeping the stitches in
for too long,
there isn't any inflammation.
I'm sorry. I've been a bit out of it.
I do understand.
I'll prescribe you antibiotics
just in case.
If you get an inflammation or pus,
come and see me immediately.
I will.
Oh, right.
Lee Hwa-jin came back.
Oh, I've been meaning to ask
about her symptoms.
She says she suddenly faints sometimes.
Yes. It's a vasovagal syncope symptom.
The symptom itself is an illness in a way.
Is there no prodrome at all?
No, and that makes it more problematic.
There isn't a treatment either.
It's often hereditary.
For example, if the mom has the symptom,
the daughter has it too.
I heard she was admitted to the hospital.
Does she have
any other issue beside fainting?
She's fine.
We're trying to solve
another issue instead.
SPECIAL ACT
FOR H CHEMICAL FIRE REINVESTIGATION
You can't protect
both Su-yeon and the special act.
You should let go of one of them.
What would you do if you were me?
Who would you choose?
I already made my choice.
MY DAUGHTER
Hello?
Are you free to talk?
Yes.
You decided not to go abroad.
Have you thought carefully about it?
I believe in you,
but I'm worried about your school life.
Is everything else okay?
Dad, can you just…
not get divorced?
Do you remember I used to like a tricycle
when I was young?
Yes.
I remember.
You always brought it into your room
before sleeping when Mom told you not to.
You got scolded every time.
Do you remember what I said
whenever Mom scolded me?
I was too young to remember it,
but you and Mom
always teased me about it.
What did you say?
Apparently, I said
our family was like a tricycle.
Since we were a family of three.
And a tricycle has three wheels.
You said it was just like us.
So whenever we came across a tricycle
on the streets,
you brought the story up and teased me.
We didn't tease you.
We were proud of you.
So can we just…
continue to be a tricycle?
-Ji-yu.
-I want to go back in time.
To the time before that happened.
I called to say that.
I'll hang up now.
Hello?
Gosh, you picked up my call quickly.
Were you waiting for it?
Did you find anything?
I met First Lady's secretary.
Apparently, the First Lady met your wife
in your home five years ago.
Thankfully, the secretary kept
a thorough diary.
It was January 10. She was sure of it.
That day,
in the car on the way back home
from meeting your wife,
the president and his wife
discussed meeting you in person.
-Meeting me?
-Yes.
The president wanted to meet you,
but the First Lady stopped him,
saying Cha Su-yeon wouldn't let it happen.
That's how they always do things,
apparently.
If they have a difference of opinion,
they follow whatever the First Lady says.
I wasn't sure at first,
but that was around the time
I planted the bugging device on you.
I went through my transaction records
around that time.
I found a record of the transfer I made
to buy the old wiretap.
She started bugging me
right after she made a deal
with the president.
You entrusted this job to me
knowing all about this from the start, no?
No.
When someone bugs someone,
it usually means there's an issue.
Like when someone is having an affair
or is suspected of having an affair.
We didn't have such issues.
Then,
there might've been an issue
with the deal she made with the president.
It wasn't because I didn't trust him.
It was because I couldn't trust
Hyun Min-cheol as a politician.
I wasn't monitoring my husband.
I was monitoring the politicians
who approached Politician Hyun Min-cheol.
I was protecting him from them.
Because my husband is a politician,
and I'm his wife, and at the same time,
his political partner.
Instead of monitoring me, was she
monitoring the president and his wife
who tried to approach me?
According to what she said,
was she protecting me from them?
I asked Secretary Bang for her diary.
A copy of it, at least.
I'll get more conclusive clues
once I read that.
Buy the diary.
I must read the diary right now.
When will you get U-yeong released?
Be patient.
I'll do what you want.
Just make sure to keep the promise.
The promise that you'll do whatever I say.
Okay, I'll keep my word.
Stay in the hospital for now.
I'll hire a caregiver for you.
I don't need one.
I'm not here because I'm sick.
Okay, then.
Ms. Cha.
Can I ask a question?
What is it like to be a mom?
Is it okay
for someone like me to be a mom?
I'm not rich or educated
like you.
Is someone like me qualified to be a mom?
There's no such qualification.
You can't learn how to be one either.
But one thing's for sure.
If you plan to give birth to the baby,
don't doubt yourself.
How anxious would the baby feel
if they knew?
If you're going to have it,
don't make your baby feel anxious.
Thank you.
It's ticklish.
It's ticklish! Stop.
You pressed down my head first.
-Stop.
-You started it.
It's really ticklish!
Get out. I need to use the toilet.
Must I do the MBS interview tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
Wasn't it on the 17th?
Tomorrow is the 17th.
Tomorrow is the 17th?
Not the seventh?
Goodness, madam.
How could you mistake the day by ten days?
PREGNANCY TEST KIT
What's wrong?
You're acting strange.
What happened?
Can someone like me…
give birth to a child and become a mom?
When my mom died because of me?
Can I really do that?
Had my mom not given birth to me,
she wouldn't have been criticized
for giving birth out of wedlock.
And she wouldn't have died like that.
How can I have a child and become a mom?
How can someone like me…
Why would you say that?
You'll make a good mom.
You always nag at me,
saying do this, don't do that.
You always worry about me,
asking if I ate or if I'm cold.
That's what a mom does.
And that's what you always do to me.
That's what you're best at.
You are
more than qualified.
So don't worry.
Thank you.
Gosh, it's late.
Why don't you grab a meal?
I'm feeling hungry too.
My stomach is growling.
This is how you'll play?
Pardon?
Fine, let's.
Goodness.
Well…
Good. You're doing very well.
We're starting to work well together.
How long do we do this?
Okay, I'll make it easy
for you to understand.
The cop is an attacker.
And we are?
Defenders.
He will attack us nonstop,
and we have to endure it.
Until when?
A higher-up will give an order.
A higher-up?
Who?
Cha Su-yeon?
Yes. What about it?
I just have a bad feeling about it.
Things get messed up when she's involved.
By the way,
why do you hate lawyers so much?
Your file says you were underage
and it was your first offense,
but you refused to get help
from a lawyer to the end. Why?
YEAR 2022
No.
Wake up.
Open your eyes!
Hey.
Can you sit up?
Are you okay?
Can you hear me?
Let's say
I stole the motorcycle.
Let's say I rode it.
-You? Why?
-You faint all the time.
You can't survive juvie.
I'll go instead.
U-yeong.
Why did you refuse help?
You must have a reason.
I'll exercise my right
to legal defense.
What do you mean?
I don't want to talk about it.
Got it?
If you don't want to, it can't be helped.
What do you want to eat?
Korean? Chinese?
I want a big portion.
Chinese, then.
Jjajangmyeon large? Jjamppong large?
Damn it.
This always makes me think twice.
What should I eat?
Secretary Shin.
How did it go?
Things worked out.
Ms. Cha sent a lawyer.
A lawyer?
Yes. Well…
Oh? It's him.
How did it go?
Will U-yeong be released?
Not yet. We just had dinner.
The investigation's not over yet.
We'll talk again later.
That aside,
what brings you here?
Well, I called her for help
before I got in touch with you.
We finally meet.
Lawyer Kang Seon-ho.
You know me.
Secretary Shin Hae-rin.
You know me too.
As you can see.
We get to meet in the police station
before going to court.
Procedure-wise, that is the correct order.
Can we
have a word?
I have ten minutes. Is that all right?
That's enough.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Ms. Cha has come over.
She's with the president-elect.
I've been meaning to meet you.
I have a question.
What is it?
You go first. You came all the way here.
Lee Hwa-jin.
She's pregnant.
What will happen
if the news says the baby is yours?
You will deny it, of course.
But Lee Hwa-jin will come forward herself.
And say the baby is yours.
That the baby
is your illegitimate child.
You…
Your first appearance on the news
is what people remember you as.
Just like how they remember you
as a survivor of a fire,
people remember me
from the news when I was seven.
An illegitimate child of Cha Jin-taek
and his mistress.
Her mom killed herself,
and only after that,
she was adopted by her father.
The seed of misfortune.
That's people's first memory of me.
And now that I've become the First Lady,
I find out my husband, the President,
has an illegitimate child.
Isn't it such cruel fate?
Stop.
A girl who was cursed since birth
and cannot escape her misfortune.
What do you want?
To go back…
to the time
before you came up with the special act.
You'll stop me until the end?
You did the best you could.
So,
stop here.
Is that what you want?
You even dug up
your painful memories
that have tormented you
and got a fake illegitimate child,
because you want me to stop?
Answer me.
Yes.
I want us to go back,
like nothing has happened.
Because nothing has happened.
There's another way
to get U-yeong released.
I've seen it before.
A safe in the dressing room.
One word from me,
and you're done for, Hyun Min-cheol!
You want to threaten the assemblymen
and force them to vote in favor?
You should stop here.
Whoever stops this is the culprit.
What's the truth you're afraid of
that you're going this far?
I don't care
as long as I can stop the special act.
Subtitle translation by: Sunyoung Baek
Yeeun Kim